<resources>
    <string name="credit_company_name">&#169; GTJ Group 2015</string>
    <string name="background_credits">Background music courtesy of Kevin MacLeod (www.smartsound.com/royalty-free-music/incompetech)</string>

    <string name="app_name">Card Suite</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">CARD SUITE</string>
    <string name="german_bridge_title">German Bridge</string>
    <string name="hearts_title">Hearts</string>
    <string name="spades_title">Spades</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="credits_title">Credits</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game">Game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results">Results</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="placeholder">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hearts">HeartsActivity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bridge">BridgeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_spades">SpadesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">HelpActivity</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="bridge1">German Bridge (GBridge) is one of the variants of the common game known as bridge. This game is considered one of the harder versions of bridge and much time is needed to master it.</string>
    <string name="bridge2">For each round of German Bridge, n - cards will be distributed evenly across all players; n being the number of the round. For example, on round one, everyone receives one card.  The first player who moves changes clockwise with every round. </string>
    <string name="bridge3">In the beginning of every round, the suit of the next card in the deck after dealing is the trump suit. Players make bids (in the order of their turns in the current round) to determine how many tricks they will win during that round (restricted to 0 and the current round count). The last player who bids cannot bid an amount that causes the added bids of all players to equal the current round count. </string>
    <string name="bridge4">After bidding, players then begin playing their cards. The first player can place any card he desires. All players then must play cards in their hand of the same suit unless they do not have any, during which they can play any card they desire in their hand. Whoever placed the highest numbered (2 = lowest, A = highest) trump card in the pot wins the trick. If no trump card in the pot exists, then the highest numbered card of the suit of the first placed card wins the trick. The person who wins one pot gets to lead the next pot. This continues until no one has any more cards left, and the next round begins.</string>
    <string name="bridge5">The goal of the game is to obtain the most points before the end of the game (round twelve). The gain points, you must take as many tricks as you bid in the beginning of every round. If you bid the amount of tricks you made, you get 2^n + 10 points where n is the amount of tricks. If not, you lose 2^n points where n is the difference between your bid and the amount of tricks you obtained.</string>

    <string name="hearts1">In the popular game Hearts, one of the most common games of this genre, players must plan ahead to protect themselves from taking cards that increase the total amount of points they have.</string>
    <string name="hearts2">For each round of Hearts, 13 cards will be distributed evenly across all players. At the beginning of each round, players choose three cards they intend to swap out of their hand. On round 1, players give their cards to the person on their left. Round 2: on the right. Round 3: across. Round 4: no swapping occurs. The swapping process resets itself after every four rounds.</string>
    <string name="hearts3">After swapping, the player who has the two of clubs gets to lead the pot. He must play the two of clubs. On subsequent pot turns, the first player can play anything but a hearts card or the queen of spades unless hearts has been broken (a hearts card has been placed by someone other than the first player) All players then must play cards in their hand of the same suit unless they do not have any, during which they can play any card they desire in their hand. </string>
    <string name="hearts4">The player who places the highest numbered card of the suit of the first placed card wins the trick. The person who wins one pot gets to lead the next pot. This continues until no one has any more cards left, and the next round begins. </string>
    <string name="hearts5">The goal of the game is to obtain the least amount of points before the end of the game when a player reaches the threshold of points (usually 100 points). In each round, for every heart in the pots that the player has taken, the player’s score increments by one. If a player takes the queen of spades, his/her points increase by thirteen, making the queen of spades a dangerous card.</string>

    <string name="spades1">In the well known game of Spades, partners must work together to obtain the amount of tricks they AND they partner bid. Rather than fighting for oneself like in German Bridge of Hearts, players in Spades must work together if they want to achieve victory.</string>
    <string name="spades2">For every round of Spades, 13 cards will be distributed evenly across all players. Just like in German Bridge, every player begins by bidding the amount of tricks they will win in the round. The first player who moves and bids first changes clockwise with every round.</string>
    <string name="spades3">After bidding, players then begin playing their cards. The first player in each pot cannot lead with any spades unless spades has been broken (when a player other than the first player puts down a spade). All players then must play cards in their hand of the same suit unless they do not have any, during which they can play any card they desire in their hand. </string>
    <string name="spades4">Whoever placed the highest numbered (2 = lowest, A = highest) spades card in the pot wins the trick. If no spades card in the pot exists, then the highest numbered card of the suit of the first placed card wins the trick. The person who wins one pot gets to lead the next pot. This continues until no one has any more cards left, and the next round begins.</string>
    <string name="spades5">The goal of the game is for the score both you and your partner, who is the person across from you, share to reach the threshold (500 points in this game).  To gain points, the combined tricks that you and your partner make must be equal to the combined amount of tricks you both bid. If you make more tricks than bid, you gain 1 point for every extra bid and 1 bag. After 10 bags, both you and your partner lose 100 points. If you make less, you lose 10 points times the amount of tricks you bid.</string>

    <string name="help_title1">Introduction</string>
    <string name="help_title2">Rules</string>
    <string name="help_title3">Rules</string>
    <string name="help_title4">Rules</string>
    <string name="help_title5">Scoring</string>

    <!-- TODO: Fill in the Ad Unit ID for main activity, etc. -->
    <string name="main_banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-6563321210012380/5058162757</string>
    <string name="results_banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-6563321210012380/8011629150</string>
    <string name="credits_banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-6563321210012380/2283689558</string>
    <string name="title_activity_credits">CreditsActivity</string>
</resources>
